Um, I can't remember, I...
That's fine, just tell me your full name and department.
Ah, finance. I'm in finance. My full name is Tim Brooks.
One sec. About 30 seconds later, the man spoke to me again.
We don't have a Tim Brooks working in this building.
Did you have an appointment with someone?
I backed up in surprise, almost tripping on my own feet.
I had just been in that office an hour or two ago.
What was happening to me?
I felt like I was getting Alzheimer's but going through every stage in one day.
I stared at my hands, unsure if I was in the right body.
I felt like the world around me was disintegrating.
I wasn't in control, I was merely sitting inside somebody else's head,
watching the world through their eyes.
Just then, I got a text.
I recognized the number immediately, it was that girl.
The one who gave me the jar.
I had forgotten all about it until I saw her text.
Her, hey, how's it going?
I looked at my phone, dumbfounded.
It made me angry she was so nonchalant about this.
She knew what was going on.
She had done this somehow.
Me, what the hell did you do to me?
Her, the worst is yet to come.
I was astronomically close to just chucking my phone as far as I could in frustration.
I took the jar out of my pocket.
It looked unchanged, still glowing just as bright.
What the fuck did you do?
I yelled at the jar, realizing I probably looked like a lunatic.
As I stared at its glistening glass, I realized something.
I didn't know what my wife's face looked like anymore.
I knew her name.
Well, I know it started with AK, or maybe you see I couldn't picture her in my mind.
I knew I had a wife.
I knew I did.
Yes, because I had a daughter.
I had a wife and a daughter.
I just, couldn't remember their faces then, or their names, or their birthdays,
or any memories I had with them.
I know they existed.
They did exist.
I had just seen him that morning, right?
I couldn't remember how she looked, or what she smelled like.
What was our first date?
We had a wedding, right?
What about our first kiss?
Or my daughter?
Or was it my son?
Maybe I didn't even have a kid.
But my wife, or girlfriend, she was real.
I knew she was.
The thought was tearing me apart.
I couldn't see her in my head.
I couldn't recall a single fact about her.
I was standing outside of the same building, but I was unsure why I was.
Did I work there?
I must work somewhere.
The rain was accompanied by a chilly wind now.
It was whipping at my face, making my nose and cheeks stink.
I wanted to go home.
I wanted to be with her.
I wanted to be warm.
I wanted to go into a shitty office job that kept a roof over my head.
I wanted it all.
I was soaking wet.
I was miserable.
I couldn't remember my parents, or my childhood.
Did I even have any friends?
Why was I in the rain?
I looked down at my hand.
I was still clutching the jar.
The only memory of my entire life I could concretely remember was that girl giving it
to me.
Telling me it was happiness.
It did not bring happiness.
It brought pain.
It brought suffering.
I was more miserable in that moment than I'd ever been.
My phone buzzed.